[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which English king had wives called Catherine, Anne, Jane, Anne, Catherine and Catherine, in that order?", "correct_answer": "Henry the Eighth", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry the Seventh", "William the Fifth", "Charles the Fourth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie 21, the team wins $640,000 dollars before Williams gives chase. Ben gives the chips to Rosa and they agree to meet later. What does Rosa intend to do?", "correct_answer": "Take the money and leave", "incorrect_answers": ["Meet up with them", "Give the chips back to the casino and fess up their scheme", "He hasnt decided"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does Chers character, Loretta Castorini, work in the 1987 romantic comedy Moonstruck?", "correct_answer": "In a funeral parlor", "incorrect_answers": ["In a pastry shop", "In a beauty salon", "In a flower shop"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these songs was not in the soundtrack for movie, Pulp Fiction?", "correct_answer": "Stuck in the Middle with You", "incorrect_answers": ["Lets Stay Together", "You Never Can Tell", "Lonesome Town"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What sea is known to be the only sea without shores?", "correct_answer": "The Sargasso Sea", "incorrect_answers": ["The Norwegian Sea", "The Labrador Sea", "The Celtic Sea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are apples associated with in the Scandinavian mythology and Germanic paganism?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Fertility", "Dead people", "Eternal youthfulness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the poem in which these nonsense words are used: chortled, vorpal, galumphing, and frabjous?", "correct_answer": "Jabberwocky", "incorrect_answers": ["Jansonaught", "Jerboky", "Jessenight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the fictional town, which is the setting of the 1956 movie Invasion of the Body Snatchers?", "correct_answer": "Santa Mira", "incorrect_answers": ["Sierra Madre", "Santa Maria", "Ponce De Leon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After an earthquake in  1989, a car thief was found crushed under a collapsed freeway overpass in the vehicle hed stolen.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This character in the movie The World Is Not Enough is the nuclear physicist who doesnt appreciate jokes about her name.", "correct_answer": "Dr. Christmas Jones", "incorrect_answers": ["Dr. Christmas Lyman", "Dr. Christmas Muir", "Dr. Christmas Evans"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The species Tyrannosaurus Rex  was herbivorous.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How large is one micron?", "correct_answer": "one millionth of a meter", "incorrect_answers": ["one million meters", "one millionth of a kilometer", "one million kilometers"]}]